goldenfrog.com 2019-06-01

# Privacy Policy | Golden Frog

_Last Updated November 26, 2018_

Golden Frog, GmbH ("us", "we", or "our") operates the www.goldenfrog.com website and VyprVPN (the "Services").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Services and the choices you have associated with that data.

By using the Services, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service, accessible from www.goldenfrog.com.

## Information Collection, Use and Retention

### VyprVPN Service

VyprVPN is a zero log VPN Service. We do not record or retain any data when you use the VyprVPN Service.

We engaged a respected security firm to audit our zero-log policy so users have third party validation of our logging policies. You can view the full report here at: [VyprVPN Letter of Attestation and No Log Assessment by Leviathan](https://www.vyprvpn.com/audit.pdf)

This means:

  * We do not log a user's source IP address (typically assigned to the user by their ISP).
  * We do not log the IP address assigned to the user when using VyprVPN.
  * We do not log connection start or stop time.
  * We do not log a user's traffic or the content of any communications.
  * We are network neutral. We do not discriminate against devices, protocols, or application.
  * We do not throttle or rate limit your Internet connection.

### VyprDNS is a Zero-log DNS Service

Golden Frog's VyprDNS service is zero-log. We do not log any DNS requests.

### Personal Data

While using our Services, we may ask you to provide us with certain Personal Data. Personal Data that is associated with your account can include your name, email address, phone number, payment information and/or physical address. Golden Frog will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes detailed in this Privacy Policy below.

Golden Frog uses the collected Personal Data to provide and maintain our Services and provide customer support for our Services. Golden Frog will also use your Personal Data to provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information.

### What Golden Frog Collects From www.goldenfrog.com:

Golden Frog collects Personal Data only through web form submissions, primarily for the purpose of enabling the purchase of services and engaging in support and other conversation. Golden Frog also collects anonymous information about how visitors use our web site; for example, Golden Frog utilizes web analytics software to track, in aggregate, the number of unique views received by the pages of the web site, the domains from which users originate along with many other analytical data points. Through the use of web analytics software, the Golden Frog website may use "cookies" to assist the tracking of how users engage our website. A cookie is a piece of data that the web server stores on the browser's PC which the web browser will then send back to the web server on any future requests, to facilitate identification of the user should they visit the web site again. While much of the information that we collect from users in this manner is not personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that users voluntarily provide to us through our web site.

## Transfer of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside Switzerland and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to Switzerland and store it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Golden Frog, GmbH will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

## Disclosure of Data

### Disclosure for Legal Requirements

Your Personal Data is never released to others, unless we are ordered by a court of competent jurisdiction to do so. Golden Frog has never sold any Personal Data, usage information or any other information, and Golden Frog will never do so.

#### How Golden Frog Responds To Civil Investigations:

Golden Frog will not sell or otherwise release a member's identifying information - minimal information reasonably calculated to identify and no more - or usage information to investigators, attorneys, or agencies unless we are directed to do so by a court of competent jurisdiction in the matter. If there is a hearing in court, the member will be notified so they will have an opportunity to contest the surrender of personal information.

#### How Golden Frog Responds To Criminal Investigations:

Golden Frog cooperates fully with law enforcement agencies, yet there must still be a subpoena before Golden Frog provides a member's identifying information - minimal information reasonably calculated to identify and no more. In a criminal investigation Golden Frog is required by the Law to not divulge the fact of the investigation to the member.

### Third Party Payment Processors

We use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors). If you use a credit card that information will be collected by the payment processor. We do not collect or store your credit card number.

## Your Rights

Golden Frog, GmbH aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the required changes.

If you wish to be removed from our systems, please contact us at [support@goldenfrog.com](mailto:support@goldenfrog.com).

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

## Children's Privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@goldenfrog.com](mailto:support@goldenfrog.com).
